JUSTIN SPLINTER

JUSTINSPLINTER.COM

mobile: 651.894.2406 | justinsplinter@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

I am a graphic and web designer that pushes the limits. I am a driven, ambitious, and resourceful designer with 10+ years management experience. I positively and proactively design, develop, and maintain all website needs, in addition to any additional design work.

SKILLSET

Web designer and developer I design and develop engaging, innovative, and fresh websites.

Extensive visual and merchandising ability Adept at many aspects of merchandising including graphic design, sales-based merchandising, and comprehensive understanding of product placement and detail.

Logo and graphic design I have designed logos for clients ranging from new non-profits (ArtWest) to the Minneapolis Downtown Council (Chameleon Consortium) to a local theatre company (SOS Theater) to government (Northwest Crossing).

Skillset: Adobe Creative Cloud, Microsoft Office, HTML 5, CSS 3, WordPress, WordPress custom theming, PHP, vanilla Javascript

EDUCATION

A.A.S in Web and Interactive Media Graphic Design Print Media Certificate Minneapolis College Minneapolis College January 2017 - May 2019 January 2017 - May 2019

EXPERIENCE

Neka Creative | Minneapolis | Junior Designer, October 2017-present

Graphic design for a local firm with a focus on inclusivity. A diverse client and project based including web design, print, and digital media

- Promoted from intern to designer in January 2018.
- Web designer for clients including DEED and the State of Minnesota (CareerForce), City of Minneapolis (Green Minneapolis), the Minneapolis Downtown Council (Chameleon Consortium) and culinary (Junita's Jar).
- Multi-faceted input into all aspects of the business including video production, conference calls, social media, brainstorming sessions, and marketing.

A|X Armani Exchange | Mall of America, Bloomington | Store Manager, June 2011-February 2017

Oversees and responsible for all aspects of the business, including sales generation, operational processes, inventory control, loss prevention, growth and development of management team and sales associates.

- Recognized as Manager of the Month, North Region, July 2011 and August 2012. Promoted from Associate Manager to Store Sales Manager, June 2011.
- Store sales rank in top 10% in multiple categories YTD comp growth, percentage of sales associates on staff achieving sales incentive, amd personal sales-per-hour. Year to year increases in both conversion percentage and average dollar sale.